affinitylive.com 2013-05-16

# Privacy Policy » AffinityLive - integrated CRM, Project Management, Issue Tracking, Time Billing & Resource Management for Digital Marketers, MSPs & Professional Services

This privacy statement describes how **Hiive Systems** collects and uses the personal information you provide on **AffinityLive**. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your information and how you can access and update this information.

[TRUSTe](http://privacy.truste.com/privacy-policy/Hiive-Systems/google_apps/AffinityLive_Suite.html) has reviewed and certified the web-based version of this application that is accessed through any internet browser. This privacy statement does not cover independent versions of this application, such as mobile apps.

## Collection and Use

We collect the following personal information from you:

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Information about your business such as company name, company size, or business type
  * Information from integrated services that you specifically authorize, including for example your Google Apps (such Google Contacts or your Email)

We use this information to:

  * Facilitate and administer business services
  * Allow you to utilize and import information into other third party applications
  * If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us
  * Send you service updates and marketing communications. You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails

Â 

We collect the following personal information from you

Information from your Google Apps such as Google Docs or Google Contacts

Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number

Information about your business such as company name, company size, or business type

We use this information to

Facilitate and administer business services you have requested through Google Apps Marketplace

Allow you to utilize and import information into other third party applications

If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us

Send you service updates and marketing communications. You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails

## Disclosure to Third Parties

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. **We do not sell your personal information to third parties**.  
We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as offering customer support services. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.  
We may also disclose your personal information:

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request
  * if we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice within the application of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so

Â 

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We take commercially reasonable measures and follow generally accepted standards to protect the information you provide us, both during transmission and once we receive it. For example, if you provide sensitive information such as a credit card number through our app, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee absolute security of your information.

## Tracking Technologies

We or a third party contracted by us may use technologies such as cookies, Web beacons, or scripts to gather information about how you and others interact with our app. For example, we will know how many users access a specific areas or features within the app and which links or ads they clicked on.

We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our app is used, improve our marketing efforts, and provide content and features that are of interest to you.

## Accessing your Information

Â 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to close your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact [AffinityLive support](mailto:support@affinitylive.com).

We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## Updates to this Policy

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our business or this app as it pertains to the information collected from you and our use of it. If the change impacts how we use or handle information collected from you, we will email you and/or your companyâ€™s account administrator, or post a notice where you first access this app prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
